# **Mashal Zahid**

# Chemical Engineer

Mian Channu district Khanewal | 03478039010 | mashalzahid124@gmail.com in linkedin.com/feed/

# **Summary**

A responsible and hard working person with management experience and has physical strength and ready to take initiative. Enthusiastic to achieve goals and learn experiences from life. Willing to contributing best to the organization and society in positive way.



Adaptability

Ability to adapt new environment

Softwares

Aspen hysys, AutoCad, MatLab

Microsoft Office

Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, Visio

Islamabad Ambassador

Fauji Fertilizer Company

Work experience

Technical Internship

Rizg: Mitta De Bhook

6th May 2017 - 19th May 2017

September 2017 - December 2017

July 2017 - August 2017

Training Liaison Training Impact

Second In Command Marketing

Markhor'16 Youth Impact

March 2016 - December 2016

**Hobbies** 

- Sketching
- Watching Seasons
- Reading Books
- Travelling

#### **Education**

Chemical Engineering 2014 - 2018

National University of Science and Technology Islamabad

3.06/4.00

HSSC (Pre Engineering) 2012 - 2014

Punjab College Mian Channu

87% marks

SSC (science group)

Divisional Public School Mian Channu

86% marks

#### Conferences

- Markhor'15 Wilderness based youth leadership Conference.
- Learn Create Lead Entrepreneur
- 21 Learning symposium

### Languages

- English
- Urdu

2010 - 2012

## **Extracurricular**

- SCME indoor Games coevent head
- NUST Adventure Club Assistant Director Admin Events.

#### **Projects**

#### **Research Project:**

Production of electricity form sludge, biomass and household waste.

#### **Final Year Project:**

HRSG and Gas Turbine cogeneration cycle performance evaluation and enhancement.